http://www.tcu.org/privacy-2

We have taken steps to assure our members' financial needs are met while implementing precautions concerning COVID-19. Until further notice, all branch locations will transition to drive-up business only. For those who need access inside the branch call 1-866-996-9828 to set an appointment. Click here to learn more.
Close Alert
DOWN
Bellwether online privacy practices
Bellwether Community Credit Union (BCCU) is committed to safeguarding information about our members and visitors to our website. Our Privacy Policy explains our collection, use, retention and security of member information and applies to users of our products and services. Online activities may be subject to both our Privacy Policy and our Online Privacy Practices.
See our Children's Online Privacy Policy as it relates to our "Save It Today!" Kid's Club, and which is issued in conjunction with this Privacy Statement, by clicking here.
These Online Privacy Practices explain our use of the information we collect about you when you visit our website. They do not constitute a contract or create legal rights or modify or amend any agreements BCCU has with its members or visitors.
Online Privacy Practices:
Advertising Cookies
How We Collect Information
Information Storage
Third Party Sites
Facts
WHAT DOES BCCU DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number
Account balances
Payment history
Transaction or loss history
Credit history
Credit card or other debt
How?
All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons Bellwether Community Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does BCCU share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes -
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes -
to offer our products and services to you
Click here to download and print the privacy form
Bellwether Community Credit Union, 425 Hooksett Road, Manchester NH 03104
Please note:
If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our member, we will continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us in writing or in person to limit our sharing.
Questions?
Contact a Member Services Representative at 1-866-996-9828 or go to www.bccu.org or visit one of our branch offices in Manchester, Bedford, and Nashua. NOTE: When you call during business hours, one method we may use for member verification is sending a text to your phone. You authorize your wireless carrier (AT&T, Sprint, T-Mobile, US Cellular, Verizon, or any other branded wireless operator) to disclose to Bellwether Community Credit Union and its third-party service providers your mobile number, network status, customer type, customers role, billing type, mobile device identifiers (IMSI and IMEI) and other subscriber status and device details, if available, solely to verify your identity and prevent fraud for the duration of the relationship. See our Privacy Policy to how we treat your data.
Who We Are
Who is providing this notice?
BCCU means Bellwether Community Credit Union
What We Do
How does BCCU protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  We also maintain other physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.
How does BCCU collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account
Apply for a loan
Seek advice about your investments
Make deposits or withdrawals from your account
Give us contact information
Use your credit or debit card
Provide account information
We also collect your personal information from other, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market to you
Sharing with non-affiliates who market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Our affiliates include Bellwether Insurance Services, LLC. We currently do not share information with Bellwether Insurance Services, LLC.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Non-affiliates we can share with include companies such as credit bureaus, data processors, credit and debit card processing networks, insurance companies, and mailing and distribution services. Our nonaffiliates also include Northeast Planning Associates.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners ancillary services such as identity theft protection.
Other Important Information
For Alaska, Illinois, Maryland and North Dakota Customers. We do not share personal information with non-affiliated institutions, for them to market to you or for joint marketing, without your authorization.
For California Customers. We do not share personal information with non-affiliated institutions, for them to market to you or for joint marketing, without your authorization. We will also limit our sharing of personal information about you with our affiliates to comply with all California privacy laws that apply to us.
For Massachusetts, Mississippi and New Jersey Customers. We will not share personal information from deposit or share relationships with non-affiliates, either for them to market to you or for joint marketing, without your authorization.
For Vermont Customers. We do not share personal information with non-affiliates, for them to market to you or for joint marketing, without your authorization, and we do not share personal information with affiliates about your creditworthiness without your authorization.
Download our Privacy Mail-in Form here.
Mail To:
Bellwether Community Credit Union
425 Hooksett Road
Manchester, NH 03104
Go to main navigation
Quicklinks
Mortgages
Credit Cards
Calculators
Personal
CheckingChecking OverviewCourtesy PayLive Free CheckingSavingsMoney Market AccountsSavings AccountsCertificates & IRAsClub AccountsSave It Today Kids ClubInsurance & InvestmentNortheast Planning AssociatesAccess Your AccountOnline BankingMobile BankingTelephone Banking Nationwide Account AccessSavings Calculators
Business Accounts
Business
ServicesBusiness OverviewOther Business ResourcesBusiness Loan ChecklistBusiness TeamBusiness SavingsCertificatesSavings AccountsMoney MarketBusiness CheckingBusiness CheckingBusiness LoansCommercial Real Estate LoansOther Business LoansSBA Loans & Paycheck Protection
Access Your Account
Online BankingMobile BankingTelephone Banking Nationwide Account Access
Community
BlogEducationNews and MediaCommunity Giving
Tools & Information
Apply for a LoanCalculatorsMake a PaymentLocations & ATMsManchesterNashuaBedfordRates and DisclosuresBanking Safety & SecurityReorder ChecksCareers at BCCUAbout UsOur HistoryMember BenefitsNortheast Planning AssociatesFinancial Resource CenterAccessibility StatementContact Us
Make-A-Wish Calendar Raffle Winners
HomeBank
Checking
Checking OverviewCourtesy PayLive Free Checking
Savings
Money Market AccountsSavings AccountsCertificates & IRAsClub AccountsSave It Today Kids Club
Insurance & Investment
Northeast Planning Associates
Access Your Account
Online BankingMobile BankingTelephone Banking Nationwide Account Access
Business OverviewOther Business ResourcesBusiness Loan ChecklistBusiness Team
Commercial Real Estate LoansOther Business LoansSBA Loans & Paycheck Protection
